A Finding Aid to the Cranmer Art Group Records, circa 1980-2021, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Cranmer Art Group records
circa 1980-2021
Archives of American Art
Cranmer Art Group
AAA.cranmart
Archival Resource Key
74.2 Linear feet
The Cranmer Art Group records, circa 1980-2021, measure 74 linear feet and document the professional activities of art conservator Dana Cranmer and her art conservation studio, the Cranmer Art Group (CAG). The earliest records date from 1980 to 1987, when Cranmer was conservator for the Mark Rothko Foundation. The bulk of the collection consists of client files that document the work of Cranmer and her studio from 1988 until its closure in 2021. CAG worked closely with artists and artists' estates, as well as foundations, galleries, museums, auction houses, and private collectors.
Biographical / Historical
The Cranmer Art Group was founded in New York City, New York in 1988 by Dana Cranmer, an art conservator who was professionally active in New York City from 1970 to 2021. Cranmer spent 11 years with the conservation staff at the Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum in New York, seven years with the Mark Rothko Foundation, and then opened her private practice, the Cranmer Art Group (CAG) in 1988, which operated until 2021. The Cranmer Art Group specialized in contemporary and 20th century artwork, primarily paintings and works on paper.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as two series.
Series 1: Client Files, 1980-2021 (55.2 linear feet; Box 1-56)
Series 2: Photographic Materials, circa 1980-2008 (18.8 linear feet; Box 56-75)
Scope and Contents
The Cranmer Art Group records, circa 1980-2021, measure 74 linear feet and document the professional activities of art conservator Dana Cranmer and her art conservation studio, the Cranmer Art Group (CAG). The earliest records date from 1980 to 1987, when Cranmer was conservator for the Mark Rothko Foundation. The bulk of the collection consists of client files that document the work of Cranmer and her studio from 1988 until its closure in 2021. CAG worked closely with artists and artists' estates, as well as foundations, galleries, museums, auction houses, and private collectors.
Client files include correspondence, condition reports, notes, analysis and treatment recommendations, documentation of treatments performed, and scattered slides, photographs, and digital photographs of artwork. Artists with whom Dana Cranmer had an extensive professional relationship have separately grouped client files from binders, which include Ellsworth Kelly, Brice Marden, and Christopher Wool artwork impacted by Hurricane Sandy in 2012. Photographic materials include slides, photographs, snapshots, and digital photographs of artwork in the conservation studio, as well as studio photographs of Dana Cranmer and CAG staff at work at various locations.
Conditions Governing Access
Series 1: Client Files is access restricted; written permission is required. Contact Reference Services for more information. Access, with permission, to original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated in 2022 by Dana Cranmer.
Conservators -- New York (State) -- New York; Cranmer, Dana, 1948-; Kelly, Ellsworth, 1923-; Marden, Brice, 1938-
- Client Files, 1980-2021; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 55.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-54, 75
  Arrangement
  Client files have been kept in the order they were received, which is chronologically by treatment year, and alphabetically by client within each year. Folder titles may include parenthetical reference to an artist if the client file represents a few artists or specific work.
  Scope and Contents
  Client files include material related to the proposed treatment and completed treatment of artworks treated by conservator Dana Cranmer and the Cranmer Art Group (CAG). Materials include delivery and stretcher invoices and orders, treatment proposals, bill invoices, shipping manifests, scattered slides and photographs of artwork, and some samples of work or treatment materials, such as fabric, paint chips, and tape. Previously in binders, large quantities of separated slides, photographs, and treatment reports are grouped for Ellsworth Kelly works, Brice Marden works, and Christopher Wool works damaged by Hurricane Sandy in 2012. Artists and artists' studios CAG worked with include Emma Amos, Ida Applebroog, Willem De Kooning and Studio, Ellsworth Kelly, Roy Lichtenstein Estate and Foundation, Brice Marden and Plane Image, Inc., Robert Rauschenberg Studio and Foundation, Mark Rothko Foundation, Judith Rothschild Foundation, Julian Schnabel Studio, Richard Serra, and Andy Warhol Foundation, among others.
  Galleries, Museums, and Collectors include Vrej Baghoomian, Inc., Bark Frameworks, Mary Boone Gallery, Phillippe Briet Gallery, Castelli Gallery and Graphics, Christie's, Paula Cooper Gallery, Dedalus Foundation, Inc., the de Menils and the Menil Collection, Dia Center for the Arts, Ronald Feldman Gallery, Gagosian Gallery, Knoedler and Company, The Met, the Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, and Sotheby's, among many others.
  Artwork examined for treatment by CAG includes work by Bill Anatasi, Jo Baer, Hanne Darboven, Stuart Davis, Beauford Delaney, Richard Diebenkorn, Paul Feeley, Eric Fischl, Sam Francis, Jane Freilicher, Philip Guston, Keith Haring, Jasper Johns, Donald Judd, Ellsworth Kelly, Franz Kline, Yayoi Kusama, Sol Lewitt, Roy Lichtenstein, Brice Marden, Agnes Marten, Joan Mitchell, Robert Motherwell, Isamu Noguchi, David Novros, Blinky Palermo, Pablo Picasso, Jackson Pollock, Ad Reinhardt, Gerhard Richter, Ed Ruscha, Julian Schnabel, Sean Scully, Richard Serra, Nancy Spero, Frank Stella, and Andy Warhol, among others.
  - Client Files, 1980-1990, Heiner Friedrich, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 1980, Lovett (Campigli), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1981, Walker Art Center (Robert Moscowitz), 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 1982, Dia Art Foundation (Barnett Newman), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 1983, Carla Stellweg (Jackson Pollock), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 1984, Barret Smith Schapiro & Armstrong (Maurice Prendergast), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 1984, Richard Feigen Gallery (Mark Rothko), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 1985, B-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1986, A-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 1986, Douglas S. Cramer (Ellsworth Kelly, Roy Lichtenstein, Mark Rothko), 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 1986, Dia Art Foundation (Cy Twombly), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 1986, Dia Art Foundation (Andy Warhol), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 1986, Gunter Sachs (Andy Warhol), 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 1986, K-T, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 1986-1989, Robert Rauschenberg and Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 1986-1987, Andy Warhol Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 1987, A-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1987, Dia Art Foundation (Blinky Palermo), 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 1987, Dia Art Foundation (Andy Warhol, "Skulls"), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 1987, K-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1987-1990, Mark Rothko Estate (Mark Rothko), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 1987, S-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 1987-1993, Richard Serra and Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 1987-1989, Viart Corporation, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 1987-1995, Weatherspoon Art Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26-28)
  - Client Files, 1988-1990, Gallery Urban, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 1988, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 1988, C-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 1988, Castelli Graphics, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 1988, Dia Art Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, 1988, F-H F-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Client Files, 1988, IBM Armonk, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Client Files, 1988, J-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Client Files, 1988, John MacWhinnie (Fairfield Porter), 1988, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Client Files, 1988, The Menil Collection, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Client Files, 1988, Kiriki D. Metzo (Julio De Diego), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Client Files, 1988, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Client Files, 1988, Mark Rothko Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Client Files, 1988, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Client Files, 1988, Smorgon Family Collection (Eric Fischl), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Client Files, 1988-1993, Emily Spiegel, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Client Files, 1988, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Client Files, 1988-1989, Andy Warhol Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Client Files, 1988-1989, Andy Warhol Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1989, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 1989, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1989, Vrej Baghoomian, Inc. (Jean-Michel Basquiat), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 1989, C-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 1989, Castelli Gallery (Roy Lichtenstein and Richard Serra), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 1989, Crozier Fine Arts ("IBM: World" Exhibition, August 1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 1989, H-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 1989, M-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1989-1995, Brice Marden and Plane Image, Inc. (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 1989, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 1989-1990, Christopher Rothko and Kate Rothko Prizel (Mark Rothko, "Multiforms" Exhibition, Pace Gallery), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 1989, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 1989, Julian Schnabel ("Fox Farm" Series), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 1989, Julian Schnabel (Francis Picabia, Pablo Picasso, Julian Schnabel), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 1989, T-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 1990, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1990, AFA, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 1990, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 1990, Vreg Baghoomian, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1990, Mary Boone Gallery (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 1990, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 1990, Carillon Importers, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 1990, D-F, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 1990-1992, Office of Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 1990, Dia Art Foundation, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 1990, Anthony d'Offay (Andy Warhol), 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 1990, Louise Fishman, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 1990, Marcel Fleiss (Keith Haring), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 1990, G-I, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 1990, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, 1990, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Client Files, 1990, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
  - Client Files, 1990, Estate of Lydia Winston Malbin and Judson Art Warehouse, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Client Files, 1990, Estate of Lydia Winston Malbin and Ralph Lerner (Gino Severini), 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Client Files, 1990, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Client Files, 1990, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Client Files, 1990, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Client Files, 1990, Robert Rauschenberg (Rauschenberg and De Kooning), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1990-1994, The Rubell Collections (Jose Maria Sicilia), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 1990, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1990, U-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 1991, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 1991, AFA, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 1991, Richard Avedon Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 1991, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 1991, Mary Boone (Agnes Martin), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1991, Philippe Briet (Beauford Delaney), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 1991, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 1991, Carillon Importers, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 1991, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 1991, Jeffrey Deitch, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 1991, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 1991, Ronald Feldman Gallery (Ida Applebroog), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 1991, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 1991, H-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1991, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 1991, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 1991-1995, Noguchi Garden Museum and Isamu Noguchi Foundation, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
  - Client Files, 1991-1992, Judith and Gyora Novak, 1991-1992, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23-25)
  - Client Files, 1991, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
  - Client Files, 1991, Q-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 1991, Robert Rauschenberg (Knoedler Exhibition), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 1991, Robert Rauschenberg, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 1991, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 1991, T-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 1991-1993, Andy Warhol Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, 1992, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Client Files, 1992, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Client Files, 1992, Marieluise Black (Joseph Bueys), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Client Files, 1992, Philippe Briet Gallery (Beauford Delaney), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Client Files, 1992, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Client Files, 1992, CDS Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Client Files, 1992, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1992, Jeffrey Deitch, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 1992, El Museo del Barrio, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1992, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 1992, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 1992, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 1992, J-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 1992, Marion Kahan (Mark Rothko), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 1992, Sally Levy (Levy v. Levy), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1992, Locksley-Shea Gallery, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 1992, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 1992, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 1992, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 1992, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 1992-1993, Robert Rauschenberg and Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 1992, Ernestine and Herbert Ruben, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1992, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 1992, Julian Schnabel (Jean-Michel Basquiat and Andy Warhol), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 1992-1994, Pat Steir, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1992, V-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 1993, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 1993, American Stock Exchange (Claire Khalil), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 1993, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 1993, Ambassador Roger Bar, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 1993, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
  - Client Files, 1993, Citibank, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 1993, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 1993, Jeffrey Deitch, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 1993, Office of Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 1993, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, 1993, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Client Files, 1993, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Client Files, 1993, Beth Humphrey (Ralph Humphrey), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Client Files, 1993, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1993, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 1993, Locksley-Shea Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1993, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - Client Files, 1993, The Mead Corporation (Ed Ruscha), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 1993, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 1993, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 1993, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1993, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 1993, Robert Swain, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 1993, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 1993, Elizabeth Williams and M.C.M., Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 1993, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 1994, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 1994, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 1994, Robert Buecker v. Stanley Taub, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1994, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 1994, C & M Arts, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 1994, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1994, Jeffrey Deitch, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 1994, Estate of Elaine de Kooning, 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 1994, Office of Willem de Kooning, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 1994, Ron Delsener (Richard Diebenkorn), 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 1994, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 1994, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
  - Client Files, 1994, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 1994, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 1994, Knoedler and Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 1994, L-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, 1994, Locksley-Shea Gallery, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Client Files, 1994, Museum of Jewish Heritage (David Olere), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Client Files, 1994, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Client Files, 1994, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Client Files, 1994, Robert Rauschenberg, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Client Files, 1994, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Client Files, 1994, Richard Serra, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1994, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 1994, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1995, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 1995, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 1995, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 1995, Paula Cooper Gallery (Jo Baer), 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 1995, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 1994-1995, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9-12)
  - Client Files, 1995, Office of Willem de Kooning, 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 1995, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 1995, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - Client Files, 1995, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1995, Wendy Jeffers and Estate of Joanne Toor Cummings, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 1995, Wendy Jeffers and Dorothy Miller, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 1995, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1995, M-N, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 1995, Maxson Young Associates, Inc. (Joan Nelson), 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 1995, O-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 1995, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 1995, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 1995, Richard Serra, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 1995, T-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1995, Andy Warhol Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 1995-1996, Weatherspoon Art Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1996, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
  - Client Files, 1996, Associated American Artists (Toledo), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 1996, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 1996, Donald and Vera Blinken and Guggenheim Museum (Mark Rothko), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1996, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10-11)